kneedraggers.com 2013-11-16

# The #1 Online Motorcycle & Sportbike Store - Shop With The Guys That Ride | MotoSport

Last Updated: September 2010

We are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information.  The policies below are applicable to the MotoSport.com website and to other Internet domains owned by us that direct traffic to MotoSport.com (collectively, "Website"), produced and maintained by MotoSport, Inc. ("MotoSport," "we", "us", or "our"). We have established this security and privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to let you know the kinds of personal information we may gather during your visit to the Website, why we gather your information, what we use your personal information for, when we might disclose your personal information, how you can manage your personal information, and the security procedures that are in place to protect the information.

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Website and, where applicable, through this Website's Customer Service Department in connection with this Website, and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other Websites that we operate or through other off-line means.

 **By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy.   If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.  We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Website and our affiliate sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or don't see your concerns addressed here, you should send us an email.

* * *

MotoSport adheres to the highest standards of ethical practices in all of our operations and is dedicated to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our Website.  **Our privacy policy is simple: Except as disclosed below, we don't sell, barter, give away, or rent your personal information to any company outside of the MotoSport family.**  One of the basic principles we've tried to follow in designing this Website is that we ask for only the information we need to provide the service you've requested. As a result, what information we collect and store depends almost entirely on how you choose to make use of our Website and our services. 

We collect and store information that you enter into this Website or that you provide through our Customer Service Department.  For example, when you open an account or place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date (together "Personal Information"). This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations and to provide customer service. Registration may also be required and Personal Information may also be collected in certain portions of the Website in which you specifically and knowingly provide such information, e.g. community postings (i.e., reviews, chat or bulletin boards), catalog requests, newsletter subscriptions, suggestions, survey responses, participation in contests and promotions, or customer service requests.  Some of this information also may be used to contact you about sales, new products, special offers, and new site features. You will always have an opportunity to opt out of receiving these promotional communications in connection with this Website.

Through your use of the Website, we may also gather certain information that does not identify you individually ("Anonymous Information" or "traffic data").  We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this Website. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this Website. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Website and to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience.  We may also combine this information with your Personal Information in order to provide you with a more targeted and personalized shopping experience. 

We never use or install spyware on your computer, nor do we use spyware to retrieve information from your computer.

Like many Websites, we use "cookies", which are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. Cookies help us to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this Website without checking out and send you reminder e-mail about your shopping orders and other shopping opportunities. For the Website to run properly, you must leave cookies "turned on." You may also get cookies from companies advertising on our behalf.  This is very common and used by many large Internet companies.  We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our Privacy Policy.  <

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources, to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you and, if you have agreed to receive e-mail from us, send you reminders about shopping opportunities. 

We collect e-mail addresses and, in some cases, zip codes of all users who subscribe to our weekly newsletter.  Except to our third party agents (as described below), this information is not shared with any third parties for any purposes.  Anyone who no longer wishes to receive this newsletter can, at any time, follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions located within each newsletter.

We do not sell or ship any items ordered through this Website directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 13, nor do we collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should use this Website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us.  Our Website is not intentionally targeted to children under the age of 13.  Children under the age of 13 should not use our Website.  In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age, and any information we receive from individuals we believe to be minors will be purged from our database. 

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not use or disclose your Personal Information collected online to any companies not affiliated with us. 

We may use your Personal Information to fulfill orders, provide customer service, track your compliance with the Website's rules and regulations, or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when you provide the information).  We reserve the right to publicly post feedback that you provide to us regarding the Website and our business.  To the extent that this feedback includes Personal Information, we will use reasonable efforts to limit the disclosure of such Personal Information (e.g. only including your first name, city and state).

We use Anonymous Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our readers are so we can improve our Website and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many people as possible.  We also use Anonymous Information to provide statistical "ratings" information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Website.  We may also use or share Anonymous Information (or other information, other than Personal Information) in any other manner that we deem appropriate or necessary.

We occasionally have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners that perform functions on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, advertising agencies, credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, providing customer service, fraud protection etc.  These entities have access to the Personal Information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that Personal Information.  They are prohibited from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to MotoSport.

Third party services that are provided directly to you through our Website, such as the "Bill Me Later" service, may collect different information and have different terms and conditions, including different privacy policies, with regard to such information. Please read those third party terms and conditions carefully before providing sensitive information. 

We may share Anonymous Information with our partners and others from time to time. Examples of such Anonymous Information include the number of users who visited this Website during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this Website. This Anonymous Information generally is shared in an aggregated form.  We may also share Personal Information with trusted partners who we believe have products or services that would be of interest to you and would provide the same high level of service that you expect from MotoSport.

We may also use or disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, the users of the Website, or the public.

The importance of security for all Personal Information associated with you is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers.  Personal Information collected by our websites is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public.  In many instances, such as in the case of credit card numbers and all on-line purchases, the Personal Information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction.  Only those employees who need access to your Personal Information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution. 

To protect the security of your information during transmission, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Most browsers will give a visual indication of when your connection is secure. For example, Internet Explorer will show a padlock icon in the lower right of the browser window.  If you place an order through this Website, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an email address and password. You must provide an appropriate email address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personal information further, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel your password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your password, please contact this Website's Customer Service Department by email (Contact us) or by phone at 1-866-333-8033.

While we try our best to safeguard your Personal Information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

This Website may contain links to other Websites operated by MotoSport, affiliates of MotoSport or third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy for MotoSport.com do not apply to information gathered through these other Websites. These other sites may also send their own cookies to you, collect your data or solicit your personal information.  Always be aware of where you end up.  We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other websites.  We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every Website that you visit.

When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to this Website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed, if it is different than as described in this Privacy Policy.  Personal Information will be collected only if you voluntarily submit it to our sponsors or us.

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards or feedback sections, becomes public, and therefore this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public.  Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any Personal Information that you expect to keep private.

The Website is published in the United Statesand is intended for users from the United States. U. S.law shall govern in any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise.

We may change MotoSport's ownership or corporate organization, or be acquired by or merged with another company while providing the Website and Services.  As a result, please be aware that we may transfer or assign your information to an affiliate or another company as a part of any merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control or organization.  Under such circumstances, MotoSport would to the extent reasonably possible require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy as it may be amended from time to time.

We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.  We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use our website in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.  At the beginning of the Privacy Policy we provide the date on which the Privacy Policy was last updated. 

There are several ways in which you can manage your Personal Information.  When you set up an account with us, or click on "View/Update My Profile" within the "Customer Service" section, you will have an opportunity to provide or update your billing and shipping information. 

You may also manage your e-mail newsletter subscriptions and your e-mail preferences and information by following the "Unsubscribe" or "Update Your Preferences" instructions contained in the promotional emails we send you. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the MotoSport.com Customer Service; 7655 SW Mohawk St., Tualatin, OR 97062, or send an email to sales@MotoSport.com. 

We may use your information to notify you of important changes to the Website or Services, or provide you with our email newsletter or special offers.  If you do not want to receive such information, you may use the following options to opt out of receiving future communications:

  1. Send an email to sales@MotoSport.com with the word "Remove" in the subject field; or
  2. Send mail to the following postal address:

Sales  
Attn: Remove  
MotoSport, Inc.  
7655 SW Mohawk St.Tualatin, OR 97062

Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, newsletters, or special offers.
